Okay, let's go to the middle one.
じゃあ、真ん中の方にね
At first, it looks like a consent form for losing the war, so
最初ですね、失戦承諾書みたいな感じになってますので、
Could you please write your name here?
ここにちょっと名前を書いてもらっていいですか?
Yes, thank you.
はい、ありがとうございます
Are you the type of person who laughs when you're nervous?
緊張すると笑っちゃうタイプの人ですか?
I'm laughing.
笑っちゃいます
I don't think there are many opportunities like this.
なかなかね、こういう機会ないと思うんですけどね
Hey, I have a few questions,
ちょっとね、いろいろ質問事項があって、
I would like you to listen to me and answer me.
ちょっと聞いて答えていただきたいなと思うんですけど、
Can I do some naughty things with you?
ちょっとやらしいこといろいろしてもいいですかね?
Well then, first of all.
じゃあですね、まずですね
My first experience was at the age of 16.
初体験、16歳です
Oh, isn't it quite early?
お、だいぶ早いんじゃないですか?
Is it early?
早いんですかね
What do you think?
どうなんですかね?
No, it's something that fits in my mind.
いや、僕の中では入るものです
What kind of person was your first experience partner?
初体験のお相手の方って、どんな方だったんですか?
What kind of person are you?
どんな方?
A senior, a junior, or a much older, dandy guy.
先輩か、後輩か、またまただいぶ年上のダンディーな男の人とか
Same age.
同い年ね
That's right, when you meet someone for the first time, it's usually someone from the same age group.
そうですよね、初めての人って、同じ年代の人になっちゃいます
Right.
よね
Do you remember?
覚 えてます?
I remember.
覚えてます
Can you tell me a little bit about it?
ちょっと語ってもらってもいいですか?
Do you want me to tell you?
語ってもらう?
Isn't that the best memory?
最高の思い出じゃないですか
What?
何を?
So, who invited you?
じゃあ、どちらから誘ってきたんですかね?
It's like a flow.
流れみたいな
How was it?
どうでしたか?
At first, I often hear from women that it hurts,
最初、女性の方からしたら、痛いってよく聞くんですけど、
How was it?
どうでした?
when penetrated.
貫通されたときに
It hurt.
痛かったです
So how long have you been used to it?
それで、どのくらいに慣れてきたんですか?
How much?
どのくらいだろう?
After a while.
しばらく経ってから
After a while, I started to feel better.
しばらく経ってから、気持ちよくなったなって感じになったんです
Yeah.
か ね
You're a university student now, aren't you?
今、大学生になったわけじゃないですか
The person I asked outside earlier said she didn't have a boyfriend.
さっきほどね、外で聞いた人は、彼氏はいないって言ってたんです
But isn't your body remembering the naughty sensations?
けど、 やらしい感覚を体が覚えてるわけじゃないですか
I think there are temptations from men, such as clubs and children's clubs.
サークルとか、児童中とか、男性の誘惑があると思うんですけど、
What do you think?
どうですか?
What is student life like?
学生ライフは?
I would say it feels sexual.
性的な感じと言いますかね
I can't help but wonder if you're enjoying it.
楽しんでいらっしゃるのかなって思っちゃったりするんですけど、
One night lamp, etc., I gave up a little due to a cough of alcohol.
ワンナイトランプとか、お酒のせきでちょっと体を許してしまった
Something like ri.
り とか
Only red.
赤いだけ
Oh, is there something like that?
あら、あるんですか、そういうこと
Can I ask about your experience needs?
経験ニーズとか聞いていいんですか?
Experience needs?
経験ニーズ?
Yes, until now.
はい、今までの
About 4 people.
4人くらい
Really?
本当は?
It really, really exists.
本当に、本当にあるんです
There were really about 4 people.
本当に4人くらい
What do you think? How many people have you known so far?
どうですか、お付き合いしたことって今まで何人を教えました?
There are three people I met.
お付き合いした人は、3人です
Ah, there aren't that many.
ああ、ちょっと数はないですね
Ah, then the one person who forgave his body was that person.
ああ、じゃあそのなんか、ちょっと体を許した1人がその人って
Was that?
こと だったんですか?
Does that mean he is one of those eight people?
その8数の1人ってことなんですかね
Why did I end up in a relationship like that with someone who wasn't my boyfriend?
なんで、彼氏でもない人とそういうこと関係になっちゃったんです
mosquito?
か?
Hey, when I said that.
ちょっと、 言ったときに
When I said yes.
はい、言ったときに
Did it feel like you were right next to me?
気づいたら隣にいたみたいな感じだったんですか?
That's what it feels like.
そんな感じ
That's great, I feel like I'm really good at it.
いいですね、なんかすっげー上手な感じがして
But what do you think?
でも、どうですか?
I'm lonely after all, so do it like that.
や っぱり寂しいからそうやってね、
I might have forgiven my body, but
体を許しちゃったかもしれないんですけど、
It doesn't seem like there are any particular men, either.
特定の男性とかもいらっしゃらない感じなんですか、
now?
今?
Not really.
い ないね
However, I do understand that Airi is a bit naughty.
でも、なんかね、アイリさんがちょっとエッツだなっていうのは分
It's here.
か りましたよ
Nothing.
なんつなく
So, I heard it there a while ago.
で、ちょっとさっきそこで聞いた、
I guess you could call it my motivation for wanting to appear in AV.
AVに出演してみたい動機といいますか、
I asked because I was interested,
興味があってっていうふうに聞いたんですけど、
What kind of things are you interested in?
どんなふうに興味があるのかなっていうのを、
Can you please tell me a little more specifically?
ちょっと具体的に教えていただいてもいいですか?
When I watch AV, oh, I can watch it.
AVとか見てて、 あ、見られるんですね
I thought I'd like to try using toys.
おもちゃとか、使ってみたいなって思って
Ah, it was used quite a bit in some AV.
あ、結構使われてましたよね、なんかAVの中で
Isn't that usually used?
普段はそういうの使われないんですか?
I don't use it.
使わないです
使わない
I guess it's all done through handshakes.
もっぱらハンドシェイクでされるんですかね
But, I don't think there's much of a physical experience with men.
でもね、あんまり男性と肉体感となさそうなんで、
I feel like there are a lot of women,
女人の方多そうな感じするんですけど、
How many times a week do you play with toys?
おもちゃとか週に何回とかしたりするんですかね
I'm so excited.
ドキドキ
No, you can't tell by sometime.
いや、サムタイムじゃわかりませんよ
About 2 times a week.
週2ぐらいで
Really?
本当は?
週2
How about that?
それはどうですか?
Do you have your own side dishes?
自分なりのおかずがあったりするんですかね?
I fantasize.
妄想する
Or do you do something while watching AV?
それともね、なんかAV見ながら何とかするんですかね
that's right.
そうです
fault.
あら
Well, even men do what they do while watching AV.
いや、男でもね、AV見ながら何しますんで
Hey, um, there's some toys.
ね、あの、ちょっとね、おもちゃあるんですよ
Would you like to try using something?
ちょっとなんか、使ってみます?
Is it now?
今ですか?
yes.
はい
Is it now?
今ですか?
What do you think?
どうですか?
First of all, I want to see Ali's beautiful body.
まずは、アリさんのきれいな体とかも見たいな、
That's what I'm thinking.
なんて思ってるんですけど
What do you think?
どうですかね?
First of all, I would like you to take a look at Ali's beautiful skin.
まずは、アリさんのきれいな肌とかをちょっと見ていただけない
Is that so?
ですか ね
Is it today?
今日ですか?
yes.
はい
Is it today?
今日ですか?
Yes, today.
はい、今日
I heard that I have to interview today.
今日、面接なきゃいって聞いたんですけど
Oh, that's right.
あれ、そうでしたって
Oh, was that so?
あ、そうでした?
Ah, no, but what is it?
あ、いや、でも、なんですかね
Well, I learned a lot about people's personalities.
まあ、でもね、人となりはすごく分かったんで
Well, just a little bit, in doing it,
まあ、ちょっとね、やるに当たって、
After all, it will be a bit of a job where you will be naked in public, so
やっぱ人前で裸になる、ちょっとお仕事になっちゃいますので、
After all, I would like to check your body,
やっぱり体のチェックとかをさせていただきたいなというのは、
There is also one here.
こちらとしてもありまして
Well, it's quite embarrassing, isn't it?
まあ、恥ずかしいですよね、なかなか
What do you think?
どうですか?
Have you ever been photographed with your ex-boyfriend or someone using your cell phone?
前の彼氏とか、携帯とかで撮られたりしたことあります?
No.
ないです
No?
ないです?
What do you think?
どうですか?
Are you the type who likes to have sex with the lights dim?
やっぱり、電気を暗くしてエッチするタイプですか?
No, but, after all, things like this are done in bright light.
いや、でもね、やっぱり、こういうのって明るいところでやっぱり
Well, for a while,
した りするんで、 まあ、ちょっとね、
I thought I'd like you to try undressing and show me your naked body.
試しに脱いでもらって、 裸とかもお見せもらいたいななんて思
Yes, but what do you think?
うん ですけど、いかがですかね?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Would you mind just a little bit?
ちょっとだけよろしいですか?
I'm glad.
うれしいですね
Is it okay if I get the top or the top once?
上とか、一回上で貰ってもよろしいですか?
Is it all?
全部ですか?
yes.
はい
all?
全部?
yes.
はい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
恥ずかしいですね
Ah, but, I see you're wearing underwear.
あ、でもね、なんか、下着つけてらっしゃいますね、
now.
今
Think of it as a swimsuit.
水着だと思うといいですよ
What, do you go to the beach with your smartphone?
え、スマホで海とか行かれます?
I don't go to the sea much.
海、あんまり行かないです
True is going?
トゥルーが行かれます?
True go.
トゥルー行きます
I'll go.
行きますよ
Ah, if you think that's what it feels like,
あ、そんな感覚だと思っていただければ、
I wonder if it's a little soft?
少しは柔らかいんじゃないかな?
What do you think?
どうですか?
Shall I go to sleep?
寝入れましょうか
That's cute underwear.
かわいい下着ですね
a,
あ、
It suits you.
お 似合いですよ
Oh, don't you like the style?
お、スタイルよくないですか?
No, that's not true.
いや、そんなことないです
That's not true.
そんなことないですよ
Well then, please throw your clothes a little to the side.
じゃあね、服の方、ちょっと横の方に投げていただいて
Would you like the one below?
下の方もよろしいですか?
Do you also throw the bottom?
下も投げるんですか?
yes.
はい
Also the skirt.
スカートの方も
I would like you to see it.
見ていただきたいなと思いまして
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥ずかしいですね
Well, can't you just feel embarrassed?
いや、なんかその恥ずかしいのもどくできしませんか?
Do you want to throw?
投げていきたいですか?
got it.
わかりました
Oh, that's nice.
お、いいですね
Just for a moment, just like that, I just want to see the whole thing.
ちょっとね、そのままね、ちょっと全体を見たいんで、
Please stand still for a while,
ちょっとゆっくり立っていただいて、
Can I have you spin around a bit?
軽くぐるっと回ってもらっていいですか?
Go around.
ぐるっと回って
Can I please turn around slowly?
ゆっくりと回っていただいていいですか?
Oh, please stop for a moment.
あ、ちょっと止まってください
Oh, so damn sexy.
え、ちゃくちゃセクシー
Isn't it a thong?
Tバックじゃないですか?
Hey, just a little bit of your butt again.
ね、ちょっと、またちょっとお尻をね、
Is it okay to have it look like it's showing the whole thing?
ぐるっと見せるような感じもあってもらっていいですか?
Ah, that's good.
あ、そこいいですね
Ai-san, aren't you full of motivation?
アイさん、やる気満々じゃないですか?
Wow, your butt is also very beautiful.
わ、お尻もすごくきれいですよ
Can I have you move your hands in front of me a little bit slowly?
ちょっとゆっくり手を前についてもらっていいですか?
Then before?
じゃあ前に?
yes.
はい
Is it slightly open?
軽く足なく開いちゃってます?
Are you opening more?
もっと開いてますか?
Are you riding on it from below?
なんか下から乗ってたりします?
Oh, I don't like it.
え、嫌です
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
恥ずかしいですよね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
Isn't the style really nice?
スタイルめちゃくちゃいいじゃないですか?
Then please get up slowly.
じゃあそこまでゆっくり起き上がってください
My hands are savic.
手がサービックになってます
You have a beautiful body.
きれいな体してますよ
Do you know the fishing size?
釣りサイズとか分かったりしますか?
I don't know.
分からないです
分からないですよ
It's big, isn't it?
大きいですよね
small.
小さい
Is it small?
小さいですか?
Yeah.
うん
Do you know the size?
それ、サイズとか分かりますか?
It's totally fine.
全然いいです
全 然 いいです
oh.
おー
But somehow, it feels like 65 even though it's probably good.
でもなんか、たぶんいいのに65ぐらいの感じですよね
that's right.
そうです
In terms of size.
サイズ的には
It's really stylish.
めっちゃスタイルいいです
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうです
Please press slowly.
ゆっくり押さえください
No, it's a better style.
いや、もっといいスタイルですよ
What do you think?
どうですか?
yes.
はい
What do you think?
どうです?
Do you think brown is a little inferior?
ちょっとブラウンが劣っちゃったりしてますか?
What, brown?
え、ブラウンがですか?
yes.
はい
Hey, please take all of it.
ね、ちょっと全部お取りください
I would also like to confirm the size.
ちょっとサイズの確認とかもさせていただきたいです
Ah, beautiful.
あー、きれい
Very beautiful.
すごくきれい
I would like to take a closer look.
もうちょっとよく見させていただきたいですね
Just move your hand a little.
ちょっと手だけをどかしていただいて
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
恥ずかしくあることないですよ
It's a nice body.
素敵な体ですよ
I'd rather see a lot of them.
むしろいっぱい見したほうがいいですよ
beautiful body.
きれいな体
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃきれいです
What should I do?
どうする?
Just leave it like this...
もう、このまま...
plug...
せん...
Excuse me?
すいませんか?
Is it like this today?
今日、このままですか?
picture?
え?
Well, I was interested in this and applied, so
ね、これ興味があって応募してくれたので、
Do you want to check them all?
全員調べてみますか?
Let's keep doing this.
このままこれやってみましょう
Will you use it today?
今日使う?
yes.
はい
Of course, I apologize to Shine.
もちろん、シャインのほうはすみませんので
Is it true?
本当です?
Haven't you done it?
やってない?
I don't do this lightly.
軽くやっていません
lightly.
軽く
Look, I heard earlier that you're really interested in toys.
なんか、ほら、先ほどね、めちゃくちゃおもちゃに興味があるって
That's what I said, so here it is.
言 ってらっしゃったんで、 こういうの
hey.
ね
Have you ever used it?
使ったことあります?
No.
ないです
But you've seen it before.
でも見たことありますよね
Let's actually use it for a moment.
ちょっと実際に使ってみましょうか
Please hold my hand, this.
ちょっと手、握ってください、これ
Try holding it.
握ってみてください
This is what happens when you turn on the switch.
これね、スイッチ入れるとね、こうなるんですよ、
this.
これ
no
いや
ー.
ー
What do you think?
どう ですか?
Was it as you imagined?
想像どおりでした?
Or are you shaking more than you expected?
それとも想像以上に震えてます?
imagine...
想像...
imagine?
想像?
That's all.
以上
Hey, please sit down and take your time.
ね、ちょっとね、ゆっくり腰かけてください
Please excuse me for a moment.
ちょっと失礼しますよ
Is this how you usually feel?
普段からこんな感じなんですか?
It's like this.
こんな感じ
Isn't it ticking, Chiku?
カチカチじゃないですか、チク
Is it tickling?
くすぐったりですか?
This kind of feeling makes me tickle.
こんな感じがムズムズします
But, it's only the beginning.
でもね、最初だけですよ
Keep going, you'll feel better.
どんどんね、気持ちよくなりますから
While watching A and B doing these things,
こういうことをね、してるのをA・Bで見ながら、
He was excited.
興奮されてたんですよね
I feel better.
気持ちよくなりました
It seems to be extremely bitter and soft.
めちゃくちゃ渋さも柔らかそうです
It's so bubbly.
こんなにプルンプルン
This left side and
こっちの左側と
...
Which one feels better?
ど っちが気持ちいいですか?
The right side and, you know, this left side.
右側と、ほら、こっちの左側
Both.
どっちも
That's greedy.
欲張りですね
Are the breasts raw liver?
おっぱい生肝体ですか?
breast raw liver
お っぱい生肝体
Is it?
ですか?
Also, I'll try applying it to the bottom one as well.
あと ね、下の方にも当ててみますよ
Let's get out of the way.
隙出しちゃいましょう
Shall I take a look at your breasts?
お っぱい見ちゃおうかな
It'll open.
開いちゃいますよ
Can I spread it out for you?
広げてもらっていいですか?
From here.
こっちから
spread.
広げる
Please spread it out as much as possible.
いっぱい広げてください
Is this it?
これですか?
more.
もっと
Please leave it as is.
そのまま広げておいてくださいね
What do you think, Shimiki?
どうですか、このしみき
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くないですか?
Didn't you hear me?
聞こえませんでした?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does your pussy feel good after all?
やっぱりおまんこが気持ちいいんですか?
Please show me your pussy.
だまんこ見せてください
I'm upset.
ひっくりしてますよ
It felt good.
気持ちよかったです
I'll do something that feels better.
もっと気持ちいいことしますね
What feels better?
もっと気持ちいいこと?
Can't we have sex anymore like this?
このままもう、エッチしちゃいません?
Leave it like this?
このまま?
Of course, it will come off.
もちろんね、外れますよ
Do what feels good, no pun intended, you can't kill two birds with one stone.
気持ちいいことしてね、 しゃれもないって一石二鳥じゃない
Is it?
ですか
I'll give you this rice cake as a souvenir.
この もちは、お土産であげますから
Let's have sex.
エッチしましょうよ
it hurts.
痛い
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいですか?
It's a beautiful shape.
形きれいだね
You can watch it all the time.
ずっと見てられる
It's in great shape.
すっげえ形してる
Do you like being licked?
舐められるの好き?
Do you like licking?
舐めるの好き?
Are you planning to include it?
入れるのいつもり?
Do you wear it?
つけたりするの?
wear.
付ける
Do I need to be careful?
気を付けなくていい?
Is it okay raw?
生でいい?
Until now, I have not attached it.
付けないでしたことは今まで
Didn't you come here because you wanted this to happen to you?
こういうことされたくて来たんじゃないの?
Have you ever done something like this?
こういうことしたことある?
About twice.
2回ぐらい
Twice?
2回?
But weren't there some reservations?
でも遠慮があったんじゃない?
It's okay, I'm in a comfortable place
いいよ、気持ちいいところにあって
hand.
て
That must feel good.
そ こが気持ちいいだろう
Don't you call me sleepy?
寝息って言われない?
Can I take it out like this?
このまま出していい?
Can I bother you?
迷惑していいですか?
yes.
はい